smileydressup.com 2012-12-30

# PRIVACY POLICY - Dress up games, Girls Games

Privacy Policy

Smileydressup.com is committed to providing an entertaining, fun and educational service. We respect the privacy concerns of visitors to smileydressup.com.

Information we collect and how we use it 

On your visit to our website there is certain information that we collect from traffic references of hosting servers and from cookies. 

From traffic references of hosting servers - every time you visit a website, there is certain information you make available for collection such as IP address, time of visit, location, internet domain, type of browser and operating system used to access our site, pages you visit, if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website etc . We, like other operators, collect this information and use it for visitors statistics and to improve our services to you. 

From Cookies - the sole purpose of cookies is to enhance your online experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer by Web sites. Through your Web browser, cookies are only used by the Web site that wrote the cookie. Data stored in a cookie from smileydressup.com is only accessible by the smileydressup.com Web site. This information enables us to run our affiliate programs, allows customized advertising, lets you automatically sign in when you visit smileydressup.com, and offers other operational site activities. Most of browsers are set to accept cookies. But if you prefer, you can reset your browser so as to let you know whenever you receive a cookie or even to refuse cookies. However, you should know that some parts of smileydressup.com website can only be normally seen if your browser allows cookies. 

smileydressup.com will not share your information with anyone. The only exception shall be in the event that disclosure of information is required by law enforcement or other government officials in connection with investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or that may expose you or us to legal liability. 

Collection of information and Third-Party sites and Sponsors 

It is important that you understand that advertisers or Web sites that link to a smileydressup.com site may collect personal information about you. The Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of other advertisers or Web sites. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our sites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other sites in order to help them provide relevant ads to users. Third parties may also be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on our website. If you do not wish for these third-parties to place and read cookies you can set your browser to block them. 

**Google Adsense**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Googles use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
